radionomy.com 2014-12-21

# Radionomy

## Privacy

**I. Identiﬁcation of the site and the organization responsible for it.**

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of anorganization like RADIONOMY. 

Our main activities are creating and providing aid for the creation of radio stations, on Internet and providingservices related to this activity (herebelow called the Services). The Services include all services suppliedby the Site, particularly: hosting services, enhancement and provision of multimedia content, communicationbetween Users, making tools available, and more generally any other service proposed by the Site. The Services also include communications intended for Users particularly administrative messages, newsletters pertaining to the Services and forums/blogs. 

In this context, RADIONOMY undertakes to scrupulously respect Belgian legislation concerning protection ofpersonal data. This legislation is available in full on the site of the Privacy Commission: [ http:// ](http://www.privacycommission.be/) [ www.privacycommission.be  ](http://www.privacycommission.be/)

Our policy with regard to privacy applies to RADIONOMY and to its web site [www.radionomy.com ](http://www.radionomy.com/) (herebelow referred to as the Site). 

The organization responsible for data processing is RADIONOMY SA 

Address: 55 Bld International (bâtiment K), 1070 Brussels. 

E-mail address: [ info@radionomy.com  ](mailto:info@radionomy.com)

Contact person: Gilles Bindels 

**II. Authorization of anonymous access and acceptance of our privacy policy**

You can access our homepage and consult the Site without communicating any personal data. 

By using the Site, you explicitly declare that you accept RADIONOMYʼs policy for respect of privacy and youconsent to our collecting and processing data concerning you, using the procedures and principles describedin this policy. 

**III. Identiﬁcation of users of the Site**

The Site is visited and used by various categories of persons; the objectives in processing their data can bedifferent: 

Ø Visitor: Any person occasionally consulting the Site, not registered in the system, having access to thecontent of this site including the content published on the personal pages of Members, Radio Creators andContent Producers; 

Ø Listener: Any person gaining access to the services to listen to a web radio station, but not registered inthe system as a Member; 

Ø Member: Any person who registered and gave an identiﬁer (e-mail address) and a password, as well assome additional information, in order to have access to the functionalities reserved for members; 

Ø Radio creator: Member who has decided to create a web radio station by using the services proposedby the Site; 

Ø Fan: Term that describes any user who voluntarily accepts to be in direct communication with a radiocreator by e-mail and/or by chat and to appear in the list of Fans of a radio station. 

Ø Content Producer: Person who subscribed to a speciﬁc "Content Producer" contract. He makes content available (musical or audio) so that radio creators can integrate it in their radio broadcasts and hebeneﬁts from publication space to deﬁne content and has access to statistics on the use of that content. 

Ø Moderator: Designated member of a group who monitors compliance with the objectives and theregulation of exchanges of electronic or audio messages made in an organized context. The moderator notably sees that unauthorized advertising messages and comments that could constitute criminal offences are not broadcast. When operating live, the moderator takes action by giving warnings and by excluding offending Users. 

Ø Users: All visitors, Members, Radio Creators and Content Producers of the Site. 

**IV. Automatic Collection of information**

Like for every visit of a web site, the following information is collected: 

IP Address DNS Address NavigatorScreen resolution Page preceding arrival on the siteWe collect this data exclusively for purposes of statistics on frequency of visits to the site, and we do notconnect them with personal data collected elsewhere. 

**V. Cookies**

A ʻcookieʼ may be recorded on your hard disk (a small ﬁle sent by the Internet server which is recorded onthe hard disk of your computer and keeps track of the Internet site visited and contains certain information onthe visit that is accessible by that site only) during your visit to the Site. Please note that you can refusethese cookies by programming your Internet navigator either to be informed of the existence of cookies, or torefuse them systematically. This cookie facilitates navigation on our site. RADIONOMY does not establish alink between the information that may have been automatically recorded by cookies and the nominative dataconcerning our visitors. 

**VI. Data collected and speciﬁcation of purposes**

We only collect your personal data if you voluntarily supply your data. We can also collect information concerning you from other sources (public bodies or private organizations that process your personal dataand have the right to transmit them to third parties). 

The data we collect when you register on the Site is exclusively that which is needed to process your data forthe purpose for which you have entrusted them to us. No sensitive data is requested, nor collected by means of other databases. You will be invited to ﬁll in a form where certain ﬁelds in bold or possibly followedby an asterisk (*) must be ﬁlled in to enable us to supply the service requested. Other ﬁelds are optional.The optional ﬁelds are exclusively intended to let us contact you quickly if this proves necessary or to better identify your ﬁelds of interest in order to send you information corresponding to them. 

If you communicate your postal address to us, this means that you accept to receive mail from us or from ourpartners. If you do not wish to receive such mail any longer, contact us at the address mentioned in point 1hereabove. 

If you communicate your telephone number to us, this means that you accept to receive a telephone callfrom us or from one of our partners. If you do not wish to receive such calls any longer, contact us at theaddress mentioned in point 1hereabove. 

If you communicate your e-mail address to us, this means that you accept to receive e-mail from us, or from our partners. If you do not wish to receive such e-mail any longer, contact us at the address mentioned inpoint 1 hereabove. 

**VII. Purposes of data processing**

The purposes for which we collect your personal data are as follows, depending on whether you made asimple visit to the Site or ﬁlled in a form to beneﬁt from a service proposed by the Site. The data collected will be those that are strictly necessary for the processing purposes you have expressly authorized. 

Ø Visitor and Listener: 

  * o Managing statistics on visits to the Site based on the data collected automatically; 
  * o Managing statistics on the visit of radio stations; 
  * o Doing market studies; 
    1. o Managing a request for information; 
    2. Ø Member: 
  * o Managing statistics on visits to the Site; 
  * o Managing statistics on the visit of radio stations. 
  * o Managing the ﬁle of members 
  * o Doing market studies; 
  * o Managing a request for information; 
  * o Sending promotional information corresponding to your centres of interest both from RADIONOMY andfrom its commercial partners. For this purpose, you are entitled to renounce receiving any messagecontaining direct marketing in the future, without cost and without giving any reason for your choice: 

§ either by contacting the contact person identiﬁed in point 1 hereabove; 

§ or by responding directly to our partner if you do not wish to receive commercial proposals from that partner; 

§ or, if you no longer wish to receive any direct marketing proposal from any company, registering with aspecial list for this purpose by going to the site [ http://www.robinsonlist.be  ](http://www.robinsonlist.be/)managed by the Belgian direct marketing association (ABMD). 

Ø Radio creator: 

  * o Managing statistics on visits to the Site; 
  * o Managing statistics on the visit of radio stations; 
  * o Managing the ﬁle of Radio creators; 
  * o Doing market studies; 
  * o Managing a request for information; 
  * o Managing Blogs, chat, e-mails and instantaneous electronic messaging on radio stations; 
  * o Managing web radio content created by Radio Creators; 
  * o Sending promotional information corresponding to your centres of interest both from RADIONOMY andfrom its commercial partners. For this purpose, you are entitled to renounce receiving any messagecontaining direct marketing in the future, without cost and without giving any reason for your choice: 

§ either by contacting the contact person identiﬁed in point 1 hereabove; 

§ or by responding directly to our partner if you do not wish to receive commercial proposals from that partner; § or, if you no longer wish to receive any direct marketing proposal from any company, registering with aspecial list for this purpose by going to the site [http://www.robinsonlist.be ](http://www.robinsonlist.be/) managed by the Belgian direct marketing association (ABMD). 

Ø Fan: 

  * o Managing statistics on visits to the Site; 
  * o Managing statistics on the visit of radio stations; 
  * o Managing the ﬁle of Fans; 
  * o Doing market studies; 
  * o Managing a request for information; 
  * o Managing electronic communications used; 
  * o Sending promotional information corresponding to your centres of interest both from RADIONOMY andfrom its commercial partners. For this purpose, you are entitled to renounce receiving any messagecontaining direct marketing in the future, without cost and without giving any reason for your choice: 

§ either by contacting the contact person identiﬁed in point 1 hereabove; 

§ or by responding directly to our partner if you do not wish to receive commercial proposals from that partner; 

§ or, if you no longer wish to receive any direct marketing proposal from any company, registering with aspecial list for this purpose by going to the site [ http://www.robinsonlist.be  ](http://www.robinsonlist.be/)managed by the Belgian direct marketing association (ABMD). 

Ø Content Producer 

  * o Managing statistics of visits to the site and to content proposed by the Content Producer; 
  * o Managing the ﬁle of Content Producers; 
  * o Managing electronic communications used; 
  * o Doing market studies; 
  * o Managing a request for information; 
  * o Sending promotional information corresponding to your centres of interest both from RADIONOMY andfrom its commercial partners. For this purpose, you are entitled to renounce receiving any messagecontaining direct marketing in the future, without cost and without giving any reason for your choice: 

§ either by contacting the contact person identiﬁed in point 1 hereabove; 

§ or by responding directly to our partner if you do not wish to receive commercial proposals from that partner; 

§ or, if you no longer wish to receive any direct marketing proposal from any company, registering with aspecial list for this purpose by going to the site [ http://www.robinsonlist.be  ](http://www.robinsonlist.be/)managed by the Belgian direct marketing association (ABMD). 

Ø Moderator: 

  * o Managing statistics of visits to the Site 
  * o Managing the ﬁle of Moderators and their activity on the Site 
  * o Doing market studies; 
  * o Managing a request for information; 
  * o Sending promotional information corresponding to your centres of interest both from RADIONOMY andfrom its commercial partners. For this purpose, you are entitled to renounce receiving any messagecontaining direct marketing in the future, without cost and without giving any reason for your choice: 

§ either by contacting the contact person identiﬁed in point 1 hereabove; 

§ or by responding directly to our partner if you do not wish to receive commercial proposals from that partner; 

§ or, if you no longer wish to receive any direct marketing proposal from any company, registering with aspecial list for this purpose by going to the site [ http://www.robinsonlist.be  ](http://www.robinsonlist.be/)managed by the Belgian direct marketing association (ABMD). 

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we will ask for your consent prior to this new use. 

This privacy policy shall not restrict the rights that RADIONOMY may have with regard to any natural personin virtue of contracts or other legislation. 

Disclosure of data to a third partyWe disclose your personal data to our commercial partners, so we can send you promotional offers corresponding to your preferences. We will only communicate commercial offers of our commercial partners to you, if you have given your formal consent for this. At any time you have the right to renounce receivingdirect marketing from our partners. We reserve the right to transmit personal data on the request of a judicialor administrative authority in virtue of the law. 

**VIII. Duration of conservation of data**

The data collected are kept for an indeterminate duration, as long as you do not wish to unsubscribe for theServices for which you are registered. 

Your data will no longer be processed in the context of these Services as soon as you request this by contacting us at the address indicated in point 1 hereabove. 

After that, they will be kept exclusively for statistical purposes or in the context of our legal obligations suchas accounting, and will not be exploited in any way. 

**IX. Conﬁdentiality and security**

We do not give the possibility to visitors of our site to use a secure transmission method to send us personaldata. Our site and our company apply a policy, rules and security measures targeting the protection of personal 

data. RADIONOMY : diligently updates data to correct or eliminate inaccurate, incomplete or irrelevant data; 

ascertains that, for persons acting under its authority, access to data and the possibilities for processing arelimited to what is needed by these persons for the exercise of their duties, or corresponds to the needs of theservice; informs persons acting under its authority of the provisions of Belgian law and implementing decrees, as wellas any pertinent requirements concerning protection of privacy in the processing of personal data;ascertains compliance of programmes used for automatic processing of personal data with the terms of thedeclaration to the Privacy Commission, and monitors the regularity of their application;ascertains that any person who has access to private data under the authority of the organizationresponsible for processing data or that of a subcontractor, and the subcontractor itself, can only process such data on instructions from the organization responsible for processing data, except in the case of anobligation imposed by or in virtue of the law, a decree or a court order.takes the necessary technical and organizational measures, and obliges its subcontractors and partners todo the same, to protect personal data from accidental or unauthorized destruction, accidental loss and from modiﬁcation, access or any other processing of data of a personal nature. These measures ensure an adequate level of protection in view, on one hand, of the state of techniques in the ﬁeld and the costs entailed for the application of these measures and, on the other hand, of the nature of the data to beprotected and the potential risks. 

**X. When processing is entrusted to a subcontractor, RADIONOMY**

will choose a subcontractor that provides sufﬁcient guarantees with regard to technical and organizational security measures concerning processing; will ensure compliance of these measures particularly by stipulation of contractual terms; in the contract, will determine the subcontractor's liability to the organization responsible for processing personal data; will agree with any subcontractor that such subcontractor will act only on the instructions of the organization responsible for the processing and is bound by the same obligations as those binding the organization responsible for the processing in application of the law; will set down in writing or in an electronic medium the elements of the contract concerning protection of data and the requirements on security measures. 

**XI. Access to your personal data processed by RADIONOMY**

You can ask us, by sending a letter by post to the contact person mentioned hereabove, whether we detainpersonal information concerning you. We will request proof of your identity (copy of identity card or passport)to be sure to respect your personal data and not to send them to a third party. We will accept only one request per year per person. The information that we hold concerning you, or a notice specifying that we donot hold any data concerning you, will be sent without cost within two months of your request. You have the possibility to challenge the data that we hold concerning you and to have them deleted, corrected, modiﬁedor completed. 

Newsletters, emails, mailings and correspondence that you receive will always mention the possibility ofrenouncing receipt of any message in the future and modifying your personal data if necessary. 

**XII. Contact points for protection of privacy**

For any question or problem concerning our policy for the protection of privacy, please contact the contactperson whose name is given in point 1 here above. 

If you are not satisﬁed with our response: you can contact the Privacy Commission, the particulars of whichare found on its site [ http://www.privacycommission.be ](http://www.privacycommission.be/) , and with which RADIONOMY has lodged the necessary declarations.
